
{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "What is the NIRF ranking of IIT Jodhpur in 2020 ?",
      "choices": ["65", "25", "53", "50"],
      "answer": "53"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the pincode of IIT Jodhpur ?",
      "choices": ["342037", "342016", "342009", "342023"],
      "answer": "342037"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which city is the pub captial of India?",
      "choices": ["Delhi", "Bombay", "Pune", "Banglore"],
      "answer": "Banglore"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which city is the fashion capital of India ?",
      "choices": ["Banglore", "Bombay", "Pune", "Chennai"],
      "answer": "Pune"
    },
    {
      "question": "IIT jodhpur campus occupies ___ acres ?",
      "choices": ["850", "852", "853", "800"],
      "answer": "852"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which city is called the pink city ?",
      "choices": ["Jaipur", "Jodhpur", "Surat", "Nagpur"],
      "answer": "Jaipur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What city is called the blue city ?",
      "choices": ["Jodhpur", "Jaipur", "Ahemdabad", "Patna"],
      "answer": "Jodhpur"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the faculty strength of IIT Jodhpur ?",
      "choices": ["123", "86", "155", "157"],
      "answer": "157"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the director of IIT Jodhpur ?",
      "choices": ["Dr. V. Ramgopal Rao", "Dr. Santanu Chaudhury", "Dr. Mayank Vatsa", "Dr. Sarit Kumar Das"],
      "answer": "Dr. Santanu Chaudhury"
    },
    {
      "question": "You liked the quiz app ?",
      "choices": ["Yes", "No", "Maybe", "Not at all"],
      "answer": "Yes"
    }
  ]
}